加州  萨克拉门托  克里斯托弗酒店
头儿
Hi, boss.
司机遭受严重割伤
Driver sustained heavy lacerations
以及头部外伤  但据他们说
and head trauma, but believe it or not,
他会活下去的
they're saying he'll live.
幸运的人
Lucky.
死者名叫莎伦·沃里克  二十三岁
Victim's Sharon Warwick, 23.
她是从914号房的阳台摔下来的
She went off of a balcony, Room 914.
瑞斯比现在正跟鉴证小组在上面
Rigsby's up there right now with the forensics team.
从死者脸颊上的淤青和被撕开的背心来看
Now off the bruise on the cheek and the ripped vest,
这是起谋杀案
we're thinking it's murder.
她是餐厅服务员
Catering staff?
事实上  她是剧组成员
Actually, she was a cast member.
音乐剧《火炬》
Show's called "Torch".
讲述了上世纪五十年代纽约一家夜总会中
It's a story about intersecting lives and loves
生命与爱情相互交织的故事
in a New York night club in the 1950s.
今晚的晚宴是为演出募款
The event tonight was a fund-raiser for the show.
多名目击者称死者死亡时间是晚上八点零一分
Multiple witnesses say the time of death is 8:01 p.m.,
就在表演正要开始的时候
right when the performance was set to begin.
上面发生了什么事
Well, what was she doing up there?
目前还不清楚
We don't know yet.
是制片人沃伦·道奇认出她的
She was I.D.'d by Warren Dodge, the producer.
他跟导演在里面
He's in there with the director.
好的
All right.
可怜的莎伦
Poor Sharon.
悲剧  太悲剧了
Tragedy. Absolute tragedy.
但我们要重整旗鼓
But you know what? We're gonna regroup,
我们会度过这一切的  布兰
and we'll move forward from this, Bran,
我们会更好更强的  你看着吧
better and stronger. You'll see.
沃伦  我们的女主角正坐在出租车里烂醉如泥
Warren, our star is in a cab blotto,
女二号死了
our second lead is dead.
我们怎么可能更好更强
How do you propose we do better and stronger?
-布兰  听着  -道奇先生
- Bran, listen-- - Uh, Mr. Dodge?
-什么事  -我是里斯本探员
- Yes? - I'm Agent Lisbon.
我需要问你几个问题
I need to ask you some questions.
好的  当然  你能稍微给我点时间吗
Of course. Of course. Can you give me just one minute?
布兰  我们要把《火炬》带到百老汇去
Bran, we are going to get "Torch" to Broadway.
相信我  好吗
We are, all right?
我来处理投资方的事
I'll take care of the investors.
汉诺威很可靠  这样一半的钱就有了
Hanover is solid, that's 50% of our money.
这样就只需要担心其他那些投资商了  对吧
It's only the other investors we have to worry about, all right?
你的任务
Your job is to keep calm
就是去安抚演员和工作人员  好吗
and reassure the cast and crew, all right?
道奇先生
Mr. Dodge.
-是的  -你是
- Yes? - And you are?
布兰·麦克塔维什  我是导演
Uh, Bran McTavish, the director.
你们两位有亲眼看到莎伦·沃里克坠楼吗
Did either of you actually see Sharon Warwick fall?
我在里面  演出要开始了
I was inside. The show was starting.
我到的时候
And I arrived
惨剧已经发生了
right after it happened.
你们知道
Do you have any idea
她为何去914房吗
what she was doing up in room 914?
那块区域是我们这次演出用的化妆室
Well, we were using that area as a dressing room for this event.
她本应在下面的宴会大厅的
She was supposed to be down in the ballroom.
她第三个出场
She was third cue.
-第三个出场  -对
- Third cue? - Yeah.
我们让演员零零散散地
We had, uh, actors scattered about
装扮成酒店客人  工作人员和餐厅服务员
dressed as hotel guests, workers, caterers.
开场是布兰的创意
It was Bran's idea to start the show.
对  一个客人突然出来唱歌
Yeah, a guest breaks out into song,
然后是侍者  再是女服务员
then the bellboy, then the waitress.
就是莎伦
That was Sharon.
她该呆在宴会大厅的
She was supposed to be in the ballroom.
你们帮了大忙
You've both been really helpful.
如果可以的话  请你们在我们调查时
If you wouldn't mind going up to the room
到上面的房间来
while we start the investigation,
谢谢
I'd be grateful.
我们定当尽力
Anything we can do.
里斯本
Hey, Lisbon.
你到底去哪里了
Where the hell are you?
别跟我说你在医院
Don't tell me you're at the hospital.
我没在医院
I'm not at the hospital.
有案子了
We caught a case.
你得到案发现场来
You're needed at the crime scene.
我马上到
I'll be there soon.
你在医院  对吧
You're at the hospital, aren't you?
是你让我不要告诉你
You told me to tell you
我在医院的
I'm not at the hospital.
你到底想怎样  想清楚
What do you want? Make up your mind.
离开那儿
Get out of there.
如果杰森·列侬醒了
If Jason Lennon wakes up,
如果他开口了
and if he talks,
如果他知道血腥约翰的身份
and if he knows Red John's identity,
柯克兰探员和国土安全局
Agent Kirkland and Homeland Security
一定能妥善处理的
are perfectly capable of handling it.
我不同意
I disagree.
你这是在玩火
You're playing with fire.
还有更坏的呢
There are worse things to play with.
我得挂了
Oh, gotta go.
柯克兰探员
Ah, Agent Kirkland.
你怎么进来的
How did you get in?
这片区域谢绝探访者
This wing is closed to visitors.
我的阿姨戴芬住在十号病房
My Aunt Daphne's in room 10.
肾衰竭  可怜人  酗酒害的
Kidney failure. Poor dear. Drinks like a fish.
你一定为此心碎了吧
You must be broken up about it.
看看你  一团糟
Look at you. You're a mess.
我们都清楚你为何来这儿
We both know why you're here.
不过我很好奇为什么你急着要和列侬谈话
Although I find your need to talk to Lennon now interesting.
劳拉蕾·马丁斯枪击他的时候你可袖手旁观了
You did stand by while Lorelei Martins shot him.
他怎么样了
How's he doing?
他会活着跟我们谈话的
He'll live to talk to us.
如果他说了什么有趣的事  我会告诉你的
And I'll let you know if he has anything interesting to say.
跟你谈话总是很愉快  派翠克
You're always good to talk to you, Patrick.
但是我觉得你应该离开了
But I think you should go now,
在我们打扰到病人休息之前
before we start disturbing the patients.
这边走  先生
This way, sir.
我自己会走  这是我的手臂
Yeah. I'm going. That's my arm.
你自己有好好的两条手臂呢  放开我谢谢
You have two of your own. Thank you.
你到底怎么进来的
How did you get in here?
谁让你进来的
Who let you in?
如果我告诉你了  我下次再来的时候
Well, if I told you that, I wouldn't be able to get in
就进不来了  不是吗
when I come back, would I?
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
人人影视
YYeTs.com
翻译：灰灰菇凉 王利峥是小交交 苏慕晴天 芒果妖怪 爬爬 非燕 那时花开
超感警探
第五季
第十八集
时间轴：烟幕迟迟  luvkobe   校对/精校：灰灰是菇凉  王小麦
第五季
第十八集
特效&后期：灰灰是菇凉   校对&总监：灰灰是菇凉
有谁能进到
Uh, did anybody have access
莎伦旁边的套房
to the suite besides Sharon?
这片区域是用作这次晚会的公共更衣室
This served as a sort of communal dressing area for this event,
所以所有人都能进
so, everybody, really.
所有的演员加上我  道奇和西尔维亚
The whole cast plus myself, Dodge, and, uh, Sylvia.
你联系汉诺威了吗
Hey, um, have you spoken to Hanover?
我希望他是从我们这儿最先得知此事的
I wanna make sure he hears about this from us first.
西尔维亚  你去担心其他的投资商
Uh, Sylvia, you worry about the other investors.
让我来处理汉诺威  好吗
Let me deal with Hanover, all right?
这位是西尔维亚·克莱尔  我们的公关
Um, this is Sylvia Clare, our publicist.
西尔维亚  这位加调局的里斯本探员
Sylvia, uh, Agent Lisbon is with the CBI.
谁是汉诺威
Who's Hanover?
我们的赞助人  主要投资商
Our patron. Our main investor.
简  你来了
Oh, Jane, there you are.
这位是...
This is the--
不用介绍了  我在电梯里过了一遍
No need. I just caught up in the elevator.
道奇  麦克塔维什  克莱尔
Uh, Dodge, McTavish, and Clare,
制片人  导演  公关
producer, director, publicist.
莎伦和其他演员或工作人员有什么矛盾吗
Was Sharon having any trouble with the, uh, cast or crew?
不  不  一点也没有
No, no. Not at all.
我们《火炬》剧组是个大家庭
We're a very happy family here at "Torch."
当然了  一个好公关
Yes, of course. That's exactly what a good publicist
就应该这么说  对吧
should say, isn't it?
受害人坠楼时你在哪  克莱尔小姐
Uh, where were you when the victim fell, Ms. Clare?
我在宴会大厅
Oh, I was in the ballroom.
道奇先生  你为什么要让
Mr. Dodge, uh, what made you want
莎伦·沃里克演女二号
to cast Sharon Warwick as the second lead?
根据这上面来看  她没有多少戏剧经验
According to this, she doesn't have much theater experience.
她这段介绍挺短的
Her paragraph's very short.
莎伦从纽约来
Well, uh, Sharon came out here from New York,
她试镜的时候征服了布兰
and she just knocked Bran out with her audition.
我信任他的判断力
And, uh, I trust his judgment.
她是个天生的舞者  声音洪亮
She's a natural dancer, big voice,
学得快  急欲成长
quick learner, and she was hungry.
这就够了
That's all you need.
她有什么好处
Well, what was in it for her?
我是说  大材小用了
I mean, it's a revival in the sticks.
她在纽约已经是歌星了
She was already a well-known singer in New York.
她想尝试一些特别的东西
She wanted to be a part of something special.
确实如此  我们在萨克拉门托首映
Exactly. I mean, we're starting out here in Sacramento,
但是《火炬》六个月后就会登上百老汇
but "Torch" will be on Broadway in six months.
九个月后会成为托尼奖竞争者
And a Tony contender in nine.
演员们和当地人有什么接触吗
Did the cast have much contact with the locals?
不知道  我认为没有
Uh, I don't know. I don't-- I don't think so.
我觉得他们没有时间
Oh, I wouldn't think they'd have the time.
他们肯定马上开始彩排了
They would have been right into rehearsals straightaway.
-是的  很对  -好吧
- Yeah. That's right. - So, yeah.
那么你跟我想的一样
So you think like me.
凶手和你的音乐剧有关联
The killer is connected to your musical.
有什么想法吗
Any guesses?
没有  好吧  谢了
No? Okay. Thanks.
不好意思  他是谁
I'm sorry. Who is that?
他是个顾问
He's a consultant.
谢谢你们合作
Thank you for your time.
嫌疑人太多了
The suspect pool is huge.
这会跟噩梦一样
It's gonna be a nightmare.
怎么一开始就这么消极
Why start on such a pessimistic foot?
你为什么闷闷不乐的
Why are you so glum?
我给你打电话  你却在围着列侬转
I call you up, and you're creeping around Lennon,
试图插手柯克兰的工作
getting into Kirkland's business.
我当然闷闷不乐了
Of course I'm glum.
-因为这个啊  -是的  因为这个
- Oh, that. - Yeah. That.
劳拉蕾·马丁斯这事儿上我们已经颜面尽失了
We look bad enough after the whole Lorelei Martins mess.
列侬是找到血腥约翰的直接线索
Lennon is a direct link to Red John.
我得跟他谈谈
I need to talk to him.
你要学会守规矩
You need to try and start following the rules for a while.
如果你非要不按规矩办事
And if you must break the rules,
那就用你自己的时间
break them on your own time.
什么时候不是我自己的时间
When am I not on my own time?
格蕾斯
Grace.
见到你真高兴
It's so good to see you.
洛杉矶怎么样
How was L.A.?
学到不少好东西
I learned a lot of really great stuff,
但我不知道别人是怎么住在那的
but I don't know how anybody lives there.
能回家我很开心
I'm really happy to be home.
欢迎回来工作
Well, welcome back to the grindstone.
谢谢  这音乐怎么回事
Yeah. What's with the music?
我们的死者是名歌手
Our victim's a singer.
她被人从窗口推了下去
She was pushed out of a window.
挺上口的  是吧
It's kind of catchy, huh?
是网络热门歌曲
It was an Internet hit.
她来这主演音乐剧  结果被杀了
She comes out here to star in a musical and gets killed.
范佩尔  欢迎回来
Van Pelt! Welcome back.
谢了  头儿  回来真好
Thanks, boss. It's good to be back.
见到你真好
It's good to see you.
进展怎么样
How we doing so far?
挺好  发现了沃里克其实是本地人
Good. Found out that Warwick was actually a local.
真的吗  戏剧公司的人似乎
Really? The people from the theater company
觉得她是纽约来的
seemed to think she was from New York.
我跟一个叫波丽·戴迟的谈过了
No, I spoke to a Polly Datch.
她说她是沃里克在萨克拉门托的养母
Said she was Warwick's foster mother here in Sacramento.
她在来加调局的路上
She's on her way to CBI.
案发当晚沃里克的行程是什么
What about Warwick's timeline the night of the murder?
我已经和大概一半的演员谈过了
Wll, I've spoken to about half the cast so far.
坏消息是他们为了方便进出  没有锁上
Bad news is they were leaving the door to that room unlocked
那房间的门
for ease of access.
所以她死的时候  在场的可能是任何人
So anyone could have been in there when she died?
是的  好消息是我们有很多视频和照片
Yeah. The good news is we got a whole lot of video
来进行调查工作
and photos to work off.
演员在7点45分左右离开房间
So the cast left the room at around a quarter of 8:00
准备就位
to get into position.
沃里克当时还跟他们在一起
Warwick was with them.
她7点52分离开宴会大厅
She leaves the ballroom at 7:52.
8点01分坠落在轿车上
At 8:01, she hits the limo.
在这期间制片方
Was anyone else from production missing
-有没有人不见  -目前还不能确定
- during that period? - I can't tell just yet.
我会继续查
I'll keep digging.
在她坠楼后有人匆忙离开吗
Did anybody leave in a hurry after she fell?
有一个  迪安德拉·桑德兰  女主角
Yeah, one. Deandra Sunderland, the star.
演员中有传言
Now the rumor among the cast
她有酗酒的问题
is that she's got a drinking problem,
他们认为她很可能
so they think she's probably getting sauced
去酒店吧台喝酒了
in one of the, uh, hotel bars.
有酗酒问题的过气天后  真不寻常
A fading diva with a drinking problem? That's unusual.
-是啊  看看这个  -这是她离开的时候
- Yeah. Check this out. - This is her leaving.
什么时间
Well, when was that?
案发后半小时
About half-hour after the murder.
宾馆的监控录像呢
Uh, what about the surveillance footage from the hotel?
大厅和电梯有录像
Cameras in the lobby and all the elevators.
马上就送到
It's being sent over.
那那个投资商呢  汉诺威
What about the investor-- Hanover?
查到他什么了吗
Do you have anything on him?
演员说了他很多事情
Yeah, the cast had a lot to say about him, too.
他富得能买下特拉华州
Apparently he can buy Delaware.
在公关送来的录像中我们可以看到他到场
We also found his arrival in the party footage the publicist sent over.
我在网上查到了他
I looked him up on the Internet.
他是外汇交易员  喜欢艺术
He's a currency trader, and he likes the arts.
头儿  波丽·戴迟  死者的养母
Hey, boss, Polly Datch, victim's foster mom--
-想跟你谈谈  -好的
- wants to talk to you. - All right.
戴迟夫人  我是里斯本探员
Uh, Mrs. Datch? I'm Agent Lisbon.
你是莎伦·沃里克的养母吗
Uh, you were Sharon Warwick's foster parent?
-是的  警官  -多久了
- Yes, ma'am. - Uh, for how long?
莎伦来我家时十二岁
Sharon came to live with me when she was 12.
她不知道她的亲生父母
Never knew her biological parents.
我和我大多数的孩子都很亲密
I stay close with most of my kids,
但是 莎伦很特别
but Sharon was special.
这是你们要找的人
That's the man you need to find--
贝利·拉辛
Billy Racine.
他是什么人
Who is he?
他是个小混混
No-good thug, that's who.
他是她的前男友吗
Is he an ex-boyfriend?
那是她做的一个不明智的选择
He was her one bad choice.
你们回来后
Had she been in contact with Racine
她还有和拉辛联系吗
since you came back to town?
肯定有
I'm sure of it.
而且我觉得一周前他打了她
And I think he assaulted her a week ago.
你觉得
You think?
我不能说我知道  因为她不肯提这件事
I don't really know because she wouldn't talk about it.
她气坏了  说自己是被抢劫了
She bursted off, called it a botched mugging.
但我可以肯定就是他
But I'm certain it was him.
不然她为什么不报案
Why else wouldn't she report it?
他以前有对她动粗过吗
Had he been violent with her in the past?
莎伦说没有  但是...
Sharon said no, but...
我知道贝利·拉辛有暴力倾向
I know Billy Racine is a violent man.
当然
Sure.
当然  汉诺威先生  非常感谢
Of course, Mr. Hanover. Thank you for your time.
终于找到汉诺威了
Finally found Hanover?
是啊  他也没看到事发那一幕
Yeah. He didn't see the crash either,
但他说他回来以后
but he said he'd be happy to talk to us
很乐意和我们谈谈
when he gets back in town.
回来以后
Back in town?
他飞去参加一个艺术展开幕式了
He had to fly to an art opening.
有一件艺术品他志在必得
A piece he just had to have.
有钱人啊
Rich people.
你查到了什么
What'd you get?
里斯本从她的养母那里得来的
Lisbon got this from the foster mom.
贝利·拉辛  她的前男友
Name's Billy Racine. Ex-boyfriend.
她养母觉得是他做的
Foster mother thinks he could have done it.
这家伙劣迹斑斑啊
Guy's had a life.
多次涉嫌伤害  敲诈
Multiple assaults, extortion.
这名字听着耳熟
That name sounds familiar.
拉辛  威廉
"Racine. William."
他在演出募款晚宴的入场券
He's on the list of people who purchased tickets
购买者名单上
to the show's fund-raiser.
他去那里做什么
What was he doing there?
我看看能不能找到他
I'll see if I can track him down.
多谢
Thanks.
你两天前去《火炬》的募款晚宴
What were you doing at the fund-raiser for "Torch"
做什么
two nights ago?
支持艺术啊
Supporting the arts.
你那晚有和莎伦·沃里克联系吗
Did you have any contact with Sharon Warwick that evening?
要是有  有什么关系吗
If I did, what's it matter?
在她去纽约前你们两个有过
You two had quite the tempestuous relationship
一段相当糟糕的情侣关系
before she moved to New York.
激烈争吵  你还一拳把墙打穿了
Shouting matches. You even put your fist through a wall.
一个月前她回来的时候
Did you pick up where you left off
你是不是又故态复作了
when she came back a month ago?
别想把这盆脏水泼到我身上
Don't even try to pin this on me.
我知道发生了什么  我没杀她
I know what's happened, and I didn't kill her.
我为什么要相信你呢
Why should I believe you?
因为我是绝对不会伤害那个姑娘的
Because I would never put my hands on that girl.
我爱她
I loved her.
我觉得也许你爱她太多了
I think you loved her maybe too much.
她拒绝了你
She rejected you,
你不能容忍她的拒绝
you didn't take "No" for an answer,
你跟踪她到募款晚宴
you stalked her to the fund-raiser.
她再次拒绝了你
And when she rejected you again,
你就气不过出手杀了她
your hands got the better of you.
我是去保护她的
I went there to protect her.
保护她什么
Protect her from what?
她上周被抢劫了
She got mugged last week.
她反抗了
Said she fought 'em off
而且把其中一个抓伤了
and scratched one of them up pretty good,
但我看得出来她很害怕
but I could see she was shook.
这和募款晚宴有什么关系
What does that have to do with the fund-raiser?
莎伦觉得抢劫是剧组里的某个人设计的
Sharon thought someone from the show set it up.
所以我一听说她要去那个宴会
So when I heard they were doing that party...
你就去找袭击她的人
You went to find her attackers?
我本来是要教训一些人的
I was gonna tune some people up.
可莎伦说"别这样"  她能处理好
But Sharon said "Be easy." Said she'd handle it.
她有提过她怀疑谁吗
Did she say who she suspected?
她不肯说
She wouldn't say.
她害怕我会对那些人做出什么不好的事
She was scared I was gonna do something bad to 'em.
她是对的
And she was right.
你是说你们之间一切安好吗
So you're telling me everything was good between you two?
你和她养母谈过了  对吧
You've been talking to that old foster lady, huh?
她从来就不喜欢我
She never liked me.
你不能相信她的一面之辞
You can't believe what she says.
萨克拉门托 表演艺术中心
♪ Ooh-wah, ooh-wah ♪
♪ Why do fools fall in love ♪
停一下  停一下
Okay. One second. One second.
这里是你上场的提示  迪安德拉
Uh, that's your cue, Deandra.
再说一次  为什么我要帮你试镜替补演员
Tell me again--why am I helping you audition replacements?
因为我们重新安排了给投资商看的演出时间
Uh, well, because our investor performance was rescheduled,
我们必须做好准备
and, uh, we have to be ready.
要是我们能再试一次
So if we could try it one more time,
就再好不过了
that would be wonderful.
我觉得你不是很需要我  布兰
I-I don't think you really need me for this, Bran, okay?
我先回更衣室了
I'll be in my dressing room.
没问题
No problem!
好的
Okay, um...
曼迪  布丽奇特  霍华德
Mandy, Bridget, Howard,
从刚才那里开始
uh, from where we left off.
One, two, three.
♪ Love is a losing game ♪
♪ Love can be a shame ♪
♪ I know of a fool you see ♪
♪ For that fool is me ♪
♪ Tell me why ♪
抱歉  抱歉  停
Sorry. Sorry. Wait.
彩排是不对外开放的
This is a closed rehearsal.
我们在调查一起谋杀案
Yeah. We're investigating a murder.
那你们在这可找不到什么线索
Well, you won't find any clues here.
实际上  我们可以在观看排练中
Actually, we could learn a lot
获得很多信息
from watching a rehearsal.
真的吗
Oh, really?
是的  一个人唱歌的方式
Yes. The way a person sings
能反映出很多自身的内在
says a great deal about them.
比如说  布丽奇特  你的嗓音很甜美
For instance, Bridget, you have a very sweet tone.
谢谢
Thank you.
带着粉饰过的愤怒和嫉妒
Yes, with nice shades of pent-up anger and envy.
你应该是讨厌莎伦的
You hated Sharon on principle,
你可能就是来取代她的
yet you may come to replace her.
所以很明显  你有杀她的动机
So obviously, you had very good motive to want to kill her.
但我觉得你没有把她推下阳台的
But I don't think you have the stomach or the strength
勇气和力量
to push someone off a balcony.
你  曼迪  从一方面来说
You, Mandy, on the other hand,
你绝对有完成谋杀的能力
are perfectly capable of murder.
你手段很高
You have a very strong instrument.
你可以演莎伦的部分
You could play Sharon's part.
但你有没有到非杀她不可的地步呢
But are you hungry enough to kill?
你有那么盛怒吗
Do you have that kind of passion?
我不知道
I don't know.
别看我了  谢谢
Oh, don't even look at me. Thank you.
得了吧  你不行
Oh, please. Pitchy.
太不行了
Very... pitchy
说完了吗
You done?
完了  就剩你了  麦克塔维什先生
Yes. Well, that leaves you, Mr. McTavish.
虚荣  控制狂  神经质  自大
Vain. Controlling. Neurotic. Egotistical.
至少和...
Sleeping with, uh,
手下的两名演员上过床
at least two of your actors.
你是凶手吗
Are you a killer?
我还不知道你的名字呢
You know, I never did catch your name.
该死
Mm. Damn.
我还以为凶手是你来着
I was sure it was you.
算了  我叫简
Never mind. Name's Jane.
很高兴见到你们  祝你们演出成功
Nice to meet you all. Break a leg.
我觉得你们的歌声...非常动听
Well, I thought you sounded... great.
演员的情绪都被他影响了
He's upsetting the performers.
-我知道  我知道  -他会搞砸演出的
I know. I know. He's gonna throw their performances off.
-布兰  我会处理的  -好吧
- Bran, I'll take care of it. - All right.
可以吧
All right?
简先生
Mr. Jane.
拜托了  你在场影响了他们的情绪
Please. Your presence isn't good for morale.
大家的状态似乎还不错嘛
Everyone seems to be handling it okay.
问题也问完了  你还要待在这里吗
You've asked your questions. Is it necessary that you remain?
我们不会影响你们的
We'll stay out of your way.
你们都不会发现我们的存在
You'll hardly know we're here.
打扰一下  我和所有
Pardon me. Okay, so I've gotten confirmations
投资方确认过了
from all of our bigger investors.
他们都会出席改期的预演
They will all be at the rescheduled preview.
太好了  汉诺威呢
Excellent. And, uh, Hanover?
还需要再确认一下
Still need to double confirm.
很好  很好
Good. Good.
真是忙碌啊
Busy, busy.
确实
Indeed.
抱歉  我得接个电话
If you'll excuse me, I have to take this.
没问题
Sure.
打扰一下
Um... Excuse me.
抱歉打扰到你了
Sorry to bother you.
你知道爵士手势是什么吗
Uh, I was wondering if you knew what jazz hands were?
当然知道
Sure.
就是舞蹈编排中运用大幅度的手部动作
It's the use of big hand movements in choreography.
为什么这么问
Why do you ask?
我刚刚偶然听到导演在大吼
Oh, I just overheard the director
说什么爵士手势
ranting about jazz hands,
所以我就好奇到底是什么让他这么激动
so I was curious to know what got him so worked up.
他是怎么大吼的
Ranting how?
很显然  他非常非常讨厌爵士手势
Well apparently, he hate, hate, hates jazz hands.
而且一旦让他给看到爵士手势
And if he sees one jazzy little hand,
舞蹈演员就会被踢出表演
that dancer is out of the show.
很高兴知道这件事  谢谢
Oh. Good to know. Thanks.
别担心  你最好把这件事和
No worries. Uh, you might wanna pass that on
你后面那些姑娘说一下
to the girl that comes up after you.
祝你演出成功
Break a leg.
麦姬  到你了
Okay, Maggie, you're up.
我们到底为什么要在这里看试镜
So what exactly are we looking for with these auditions?
看到就知道了
We'll know when we see it.
你喜欢音乐剧吗
You like musicals?
没理由不喜欢啊
Oh, what's not to like?
她们表演得真好
They're so good.
还有多少人
How many more are there?
我也不清楚
I'm not sure.
有个捣蛋鬼应该马上就要露面了
A troublemaker should reveal herself very shortly.
不  不  不不不不不不不
No! No! No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
你在干什么  布丽奇特
What are you doing, Bridget?
怎么突然就变成了爱达荷的夜店风了
Suddenly we were in a cabaret bar in Idaho.
我以为你希望有大幅度的手部动作
I thought you wanted bigger hand movement.
谁告诉你的
What gave you that idea?
抱歉  不过  这可能是我造成的
Uh, I'm sorry, but this, uh, might indirectly be my doing.
我跟第一个舞者说
I told the first dancer that the director
导演会开除有大幅度手部动作的人
would fire anyone that added big hand movements.
什么
What?
请她  还有所有试镜的姑娘
And she, along with everyone else who auditioned,
都要告诉自己后面出场的人
made sure that the dancer that came after them
不要做爵士手势
didn't use the jazz hands
这样就不会被开除了
so that they didn't lose their job...
除了布丽奇特
until Bridget.
曼迪在我前面
Mandy came before me.
你不是说真的吧
You can't be serious.
只有诡计多端的狡诈的人
Only a scheming and conniving person
才会这么无情地想除去和自己共事的同伴
would so callously try to get a fellow cast mate fired.
真说不准你这种人会做出什么事
There's no telling how far someone like you will go.
他说的是真的吗  曼迪
Is he telling the truth, Mandy?
这重要吗
What does it matter?
反正你把手从中间
At least the hands distract away
向两边打开的动作也糟透了
from the dreadful syncopation problem you have.
你想我试镜失败吗
You wanted me to fail?
反正也不难
That's not hard.
你个贱人
You bitch.
瑞斯比
Uh, Rigsby?
等等  你刚刚喊我什么来着
Okay. I'm sorry. What did you just call me?
-不好意思  -拿开你的手
- Oh, I'm sorry... - Get your hands off me!
你介意去平息事态吗
You mind stepping in and handling this?
女士们  女士们  女士们
Ladies, ladies, ladies...
我还有点事
I have an errand to run.
帮帮忙
Help!
好了
Aah! Okay.
我知道你跟我说话就是为了套消息
I know you're only talking to me to get information out of me,
但是你人很好
but it's been nice.
让我很开心
You make me smile.
还有什么能比得上你的笑容呢
What's worth more than a smile?
说得真对
True enough.
列侬先生的伤势已经稳定下来了
Mr. Lennon is pretty much stable.
血容量也回升了
His blood volume is up,
明天一早医生就能让他从昏迷中
and the doctors could bring him out of the coma
苏醒过来
as early as tomorrow.
谢谢  很高兴了解到这些
Thank you. That's very good to know.
到底是怎么回事
What is all this about?
为什么联调局的人怪里怪气又神秘兮兮的
And why are the federal guys so weird and creepy?
是吗  他们怎么怪里怪气神秘兮兮的
They are? How are they weird and creepy?
好像他们表里不一
Like they're not what they seem.
好像有一天他们会撕下脸皮
Like one day they might pull their faces off,
露出外星蜥蜴人的脸出来
and there'd be alien lizards underneath, you know?
也不是没可能  就是可能性很低
I know. Not impossible, but very unlikely.
我知道  他们就是这种德性
I know. They just have that vibe.
是啊
I understand.
他们叫醒列侬先生时  你能通知我吗
Will you call me when they bring Mr. Lennon out of his coma?
没问题
Sure.
谢谢  非常感激
Thank you. I appreciate that.
这些抓痕挺引人注目的
Interesting set of scratch marks.
怎么回事
What happened?
猫抓的
Cat.
莎伦·沃里在遭到行凶抢劫的时候反击过
Sharon Warwick fought back against one of her attackers
其中一名袭击者
when she was mugged.
你知道吗
Know anything about that?
你知道谋杀发生后  他们在莎伦的
You know they found D.N.A. samples
指甲里找到了DNA样本吗
under Sharon's nails after the murder?
真是神奇啊  一点点DNA
It's amazing how a little D.N.A.
就能把两个人联系起来
can tie two people together.
好吧  是我袭击她的
Okay. The mugging, that was me.
我只是想吓吓她
I just wanted to scare her a little bit.
我没杀她
I didn't kill her.
你的同谋是谁
Who was your accomplice?
一个叫乔伊的人
A guy named Joey.
他是我在萨尔萨舞班上的舞伴
He's my partner in Salsa class.
你为什么想吓唬她
And why did you want to scare her?
因为她只是个名不见经传的女孩
Because she was just some girl
声音不错  但缺乏经验
with an okay voice and no resume,
而她竟然跟迪安德拉一起上了头条
and there she was headlining with Deandra.
那让你很恼火吗
And that made you mad?
女二号本应是我  而不是莎伦
Second lead should have been me, not Sharon.
所以当她出席募款晚宴
So when she showed up for the fund-raiser,
准备开始走上成名之路的时候
ready to launch a star-making turn,
你一时冲动  就将她推下了阳台
you snapped and you pushed her off that balcony.
我说了人不是我杀的
I told you I didn't kill her.
你已经承认策划了那场袭击
Well, you've already admitted to organizing an assault.
怀疑你一不做二不休
Why is it so crazy to think
把她杀了也是非常合理的
that you didn't decide to finish the job?
因为我并不想要她的命
Because I didn't want her dead,
我只想让她离开
I just wanted her to leave.
如果你要找嫌疑犯
If you're looking for suspects,
最好去查查演出的领衔主演
you might wanna check out the star of the show.
迪安德拉·桑德兰吗
Deandra Sunderland?
卑鄙女王
The queen of mean.
你为什么认为桑德兰会杀了沃里克
What makes you think Sunderland could have killed Warwick?
因为导演想让莎伦取代迪安德拉
Because the director wanted to replace Deandra with Sharon.
所有人都知道
Everybody knew it.
她年纪太大了  不适合扮演天真少女角色了
I mean she's too old to be playing the ingenue, right?
谋杀当晚  你见过桑德兰吗
Did you see Sunderland the night of the murder?
没有
No.
序曲开始的时候  到处都找不到她
She was nowhere to be found when the overture began.
意外发生之后呢
What about after the accident?
她直到第二天早上的排练才出现
Not until rehearsal the next morning.
♪ Every time ♪
♪ we say goodbye ♪
♪ I die♪
♪ a little ♪
♪ Every time ♪
♪ we say goodbye ♪
♪ I wonder why ♪
♪ a little ♪
是的  汉诺威先生  太好了
Yes, Mr. Hanover. Excellent.
好的  不  那听起来很好
Yeah. Yes. No, that sounds good.
好  听起来不错  没问题
Uh, okay. Sounds good. Sure.
期待尽快见到您  谢谢
We'll see you very soon. Thanks.
抱歉  你们打算把曼迪关多久
Sorry. Um, how long you gonna keep Mandy?
得关一阵子  对待犯法的人就要这样
A while. That's what we do when people break the law.
探员  我是专业人士
Okay, look, agent, I'm a pro.
我能够扭转这场灾难
I can spin this tragedy.
它甚至可让作品更吸引人
It can even add an air of fascination to the production.
但是  如果你们
But if you arrest the cast
在给投资商的演出进行之前逮捕演员的话
right before a performance for the investors,
那会让我的工作陷入困境
that makes my job rather difficult.
我得让投资商们保持兴趣
You see, I need my investors to stay... invested.
那先给你打个预防针
Well, brace yourself,
因为我要去找迪安德拉·桑德兰问话了
because now I need to talk to Deandra Sunderland.
这可真是场噩梦
This is a nightmare.
♪ There's no love song ♪
♪ finer ♪
♪ But how strange ♪
♪ the change ♪
♪ from major to minor ♪
桑德兰女士
Miss Sunderland.
抱歉打断了你
My apologies for interrupting.
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
我正在排练  我希望不被打扰
I'm rehearsing here. I asked not to be disturbed.
这很重要
This is important.
莎伦·沃里克坠下阳台的时候你在哪里
Where were you when Sharon Warwick fell off the balcony?
我在宴会大厅
I was in the ballroom.
所有的证据都和你的说法相反
All of our evidence points to the contrary.
每一个和演出相关的人
Everybody involved in the production
都觉得你是跑去喝酒了
seems to think you were off drinking.
我认为你有可能和莎伦在一起
I think you might have been with Sharon.
我认为你发现了麦克塔维什打算
I think you found out that McTavish was planning
让她来取代你  然后你很恼火
on replacing you with her, and you got mad.
他想让莎伦取代我吗
He wanted Sharon to replace me?
她在学习你所有表演的录像
She was studying film of all of your performances
并且在背你的台词
and memorizing your lines.
你根本不理解
You don't understand.
你如果告诉她实情  她就会理解了
She would if you told her the truth.
你的歌声很美
You sing beautifully.
你在那待多久了
How long have you been out there?
很久了
Long enough.
我一直在想  是什么让莎伦·沃里克
You know, I kept wondering what brought Sharon Warwick
回到萨克拉门托
back to Sacramento.
她为了自己的追求离开萨克拉门托
She left Sacramento because she wanted something,
现在她回来了
and now she's back.
显然是和《火炬》有关
It's obviously connected to "Torch,"
但她所追寻的东西并不是观众的喝彩
but it couldn't be acclaim she was looking for,
因为那她在纽约已经实现了
'cause she got that in New York City.
后来我听到你唱歌  我才明白
And then I heard you sing, and it came to me.
每个被收养的孩子都在寻找的是什么
What is it that every foster child is looking for?
里斯本  这位是莎伦·沃里克的亲生母亲
Lisbon, I'd like you to meet Sharon Warwick's mother.
我有莎伦的时候
I was, uh...
还非常年轻
very young when I had Sharon.
她父亲是我的导演  他已经结婚了
Her father was my director, and he was married.
把她送走是我人生中最艰难的决定
The hardest thing I ever did in my life was giving her away.
你什么时候知道她是你女儿的
When did she learn she was your daughter?
她在第一天排练之后
She came to my dressing room
来到我的更衣室
after the first day of rehearsals.
你一定很震惊吧
Must have been a shock.
我很高兴她的成长
I felt so happy seeing the person that she had become.
她那么有才华
So talented, so...
充满活力
full of life.
你为什么保密呢
Why did you keep it a secret?
内疚  羞愧
Guilt. Shame.
还有其它的原因
Something else.
你在隐瞒其它原因
You're hiding something else.
你真是个聪明的警察
You're quite a clever policeman, aren't you?
我在六个月前被诊断出
I have multiple sclerosis,
患有多发性硬化症
diagnosed six months ago.
我很遗憾
Hmm. I'm sorry.
疾病的症状
Symptoms of the disease is what
让人们以为你在酗酒
made people think you were drinking.
我已经戒酒十四年了
Well, I've been sober for 14 years,
至今滴酒未沾
haven't touched a drop.
我听到别人在我背后的窃窃私语
I heard the whispers behind my back,
觉得是时候离开了
I thought it might be better to quit.
莎伦很生气
Sharon was so mad,
对我爱护备至
already protective towards me.
她告诉我要坚强
She told me to be strong.
你在第一场演出之前
And you had an attack
疾病发作了  是吗
right before the first performance, didn't you?
你没带药
You didn't have your medication.
是的
Yes.
莎伦说她会去楼上套房里帮你拿药
Sharon said she'd go up to the suite and get it for you.
她是个惊人的小姑娘
She was an incredible young woman.
所以我没法弃演
That's why I can't quit the show.
我不得不继续
I have to go on with it--
来祭奠我的孩子
to honor my child.
早
Morning.
-早  -早
- Morning. - Morning.
我们查了所有的照片  视频
We've been through all the photos, videos,
和监控录像
and security footage.
比对了每个来宾  酒店工作人员
Cross-indexed every guest, hotel worker,
出席者  以及演出相关人员
attendee, and person connected to the play.
所有人的行程都能证实  除了他
All their movements are accounted for, except for him.
伯恩特·汉诺威  那个投资商
Berndt Hanover, the investor?
这是他在凶案发生前
He, uh, here he is before the murder,
在进电梯
getting into the elevator.
他去了莎伦·沃里克遇害的楼层
He goes to the floor Sharon Warwick was killed on
然后下来  之后就不见了
and gets off, and that's the last time we see him.
什么意思  怎么可能
What do you mean? How can that be?
不知道  他再也没上电梯
I don't know. He never gets back on the elevator,
也没人见到他离开大楼
and he's never seen leaving the building.
好  可怎么会  为什么  他怎么做到离开大楼
Okay, but how? Why? How does he leave the building
而不被人看到的
without being seen?
如果他等到走廊没人
If he waited until the hallway was empty,
他可能走下楼到一层
he could've taken the stairs down to the first floor.
就算是这样  他之后怎么躲过别人的视线
Yeah, but how does he avoid being seen after that?
他又不是什么不起眼的小人物
It--it's not like he's a guy who doesn't stand out.
没错
True.
这是案发的房间
This is the room the murder took place.
那里是阳台  门口通往走廊
That's the balcony. Doorway out here to the corridor.
走楼梯  下去坐电梯
Past the stairs, down to the elevators.
如果我没记错  这里是通往消防梯的窗户
This, if I recall, was a window out to a fire escape.
他可能从消防梯下去吗
Could he have gone down a fire escape?
他块头很大  我觉得他身手没那么敏捷
He's a big man. I don't think he's that agile.
那怎么回事
Then what?
对  这是个谜题
Hmm. Yes, it's a puzzle.
你怎么看上去那么高兴
Why do you look so happy?
你有办法解开这个谜题
You have a way to solve the puzzle?
那是自然
Naturally.
剧院见
Meet me at the theater.
干得好
This is good work.
及时向我汇报进展
Keep me informed of your progress.
你在门口偷偷摸摸干什么呢  简先生
Why are you lurking out there, Mr. Jane?
我要你帮忙
I need a favor.
是不是我帮了你的忙
Is this the type of favor where...
你就欠我个人情
You would then owe me a favor?
实际上  你已经欠我个人情了
Actually, you already owe me a favor,
可如果你高兴  我可以另借你个人情
but I'll spot you another if that pleases you.
你要什么
What do you need?
要你
I need you.
好  还有十五分钟开幕  各位
Okay, 15 minutes to curtain, people.
加油  加油
Let's pick it up, pick it up.
迪安德拉  别忘了在第一个前奏时
Um, hey, Deandra, uh, don't forget to wait
等三个小节  好吗
three bars in the first intro, okay?
亲爱的  我在你学会擦鼻子之前
Darling, I've been doing this since before you learned
就已经在这一行了
to wipe your own nose.
管好自己的事吧
Worry about your own business.
别指导  别指导
Never direct. Never direct.
女士们  先生们  请各位有序入场
Ladies and gentlemen, if you will kindly enter the theater
并就座
and take your seats, please.
里斯本  你到剧场了吗
Hey, Lisbon, you at the theater yet?
简  你在哪儿
Jane, where are you?
在路上  快到了
Uh, on my way. Almost there.
你去后台  我们马上去找你
You head backstage. We'll see you in a minute.
我们  还有谁
We? Who's we? Uh...
很快就见到了  里斯本  再见
I'll see you very soon, Lisbon. Bye.
我心里真没底
I don't know about this.
相信我  你会觉得很有意思
Oh, trust me. You'll have fun.
"相信我  你会觉得很有意思"
"Trust me. You'll have fun."
还有什么情况会这更可疑
Was there ever a more suspicious phase?
J.J.  你该给生活找点乐子
J.J., you have to live a little.
你每天都在抓小偷
You spend your days chasing paper clip thieves.
什么时候能有机会揪住凶手
When do you ever get the chance to nail a killer?
是没有
No, it's true.
我很乐意帮忙
I'm happy to help.
我担心的是我的表现
It's the performance aspect that concerns me.
什么表现
What performance aspect?
你进入房间
You go into a room.
如果有人和你说话
If someone says anything to you,
你就说  "哈哈哈"  或"可能吧"...
you say, "Ha ha ha", or "perhaps"...
哈哈哈
Ha ha ha.
可能吧
Perhaps.
够了
Good enough.
要带口音吗
Would an accent help?
简单就好
Keep it simple.
你们都知道  这场演出
As you know, this, uh, show
在过去的几天里
has faced a great deal of hardship and tragedy
遭遇了极大的困难和灾难
the past few days.
可我能告诉你们  这只会让我们变得更强
But I can tell you that it has only made us stronger.
-谢谢  -晚上好  里斯本  找到乐子了吗
- Thank you. - Evening, Lisbon, you having fun yet?
你来了  刚才去哪里了  你有什么计划
There you are. Where have you been and what's your plan?
等一下告诉你
I will tell you in one minute.
晚上好  真是个美好的夜晚
Oh, good evening, and what an evening it is.
里斯本  你认识道奇先生吗
Lisbon, you remember Mr. Dodge?
当然
Of course.
两位警探  有事吗
Agents, what are you doing here?
我告诉你  道奇先生
Well, I've gotta tell you, Mr. Dodge,
看了那么多场彩排
after watching all those rehearsals,
我们欲罢不能  可以看表演吗
we couldn't just stay away, could we?
好  沃伦  你该上台说话了
Okay, uh, Warren, you're supposed to go say something.
好  我知道  我准备好了
Yes, I know. I'm ready.
最后  有请我们尊敬的制片人
Finally, let me introduce our esteemed producer,
沃伦·道奇  来讲话
Warren Dodge, to tell you...
那是谁
Who is that?
天呐  是伯恩特·汉诺威
Oh, my goodness. It's Berndt Hanover.
汉诺威先生
Mr. Hanover. Hi.
真让人惊喜
What a wonderful surprise.
汉诺威先生  真荣幸
Mr. Hanover, such an honor.
我是西尔维亚·克莱尔  我们通过电话
I'm--I'm Sylvia Clare. We spoke on the phone.
旅途还顺利吧
Your trip was a good one, I hope?
是的  很顺利  谢谢  克莱尔女士
Yes, it was very good. Thank you, Ms. Clare.
-好  -请问
- Sure. - Excuse me.
怎么回事
What's going on?
沃伦  你怎么不出来跟可爱的观众们说说话
Warren? Why don't you come out and talk to the lovely people?
克莱尔女士  我是来给我的投资者们
Ms. Clare, I have come to address
发表讲话的
my fellow investors.
不如我去给他们说说话
Why don't I go and speak to them now?
什么
What?
太好了  真是个好主意
Oh, terrific. That is a great idea.
-不是吗  沃伦  -你是谁
- Isn't it, Warren? - Who are you, huh?
怎么了  等等  你在干什么
W-w-w-whoa. Wait. What are you doing?
他不是伯恩特·汉诺威  他是冒牌货
He's not Berndt Hanover. He's a fraud!
沃伦  怎么回事
Warren! What is going on?
我不知道他在耍什么把戏
I don't know what game he's playing,
反正他不是汉诺威
but he's not Hanover.
你在说什么  不然他是谁
Well, what are you saying? Then who is he?
他叫J.J.拉罗彻
His name is J.J. LaRoche.
道奇先生说得对  他不是伯恩特·汉诺威
Mr. Dodge is correct. It isn't Berndt Hanover.
好吧  我一头雾水
Okay, I'm totally confused.
我们伪装了他  帽子和眼镜
Ah, we faked it--the hat, the glasses,
手杖  大衣
the cane, the coat.
瞧  伯恩特·汉诺威出现了
Et voila. Berndt Hanover.
可是这是为了什么
But why?
做个测试  你们都以为是他
A test. You all believe it was him,
而且让你们相信易如反掌
and it was easy to make you believe it.
可好景不长  他把我拆穿了
For about ten seconds, until he said that I wasn't.
然后你们就没人相信是他了
And then nobody believed it anymore,
而我也不再相信
just like I don't believe anymore
这世界上有伯恩特·汉诺威这个人存在
that Berndt Hanover exists.
什么  太荒唐了
What? Well, that's ridiculous.
-是吗  -当然有伯恩特·汉诺威这个人了
- Is it? - Of course Berndt Hanover exists.
那就叫他出来吧
Then produce him.
你不是这方面的专家吗  他在哪儿呢
You're a producer. Where is he?
我总不能把他变出来吧
Well... I just can't magically make him appear.
给他打电话
Call him.
简先生  我手边没他的电话号码
Mr. Jane, I don't have his phone number on me.
难以置信
Hard to believe.
在我办公室呢
You know, uh, it's at my office,
我等会儿去那儿打给他
and I will call him there, uh, when I'm--
-我有  我来打  -还好
- I have it. I'll call him. - That's lucky.
-我打了  -很好
- I'm calling him. - Good idea.
-通了  -太好了
- It's ringing. - Excellent.
他可能不会接  他很忙的
He might not answer. He's a--he's a very busy man.
那是
Of course.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
你的衣服在演奏《第五交响曲》呢
Your coat is playing the "Fifth Symphony."
不接吗  道奇先生
Gonna answer that, Mr. Dodge?
还是该称你为
Or should we call you mister...
汉诺威先生
Hanover?
你好  抱歉
Hello? Sorry.
道奇先生现在没空接电话  西尔维亚
Mr. Dodge can't come to the phone right now, Sylvia.
他正忙着被抓起来呢
He's a little busy getting arrested.
汉诺威没坐电梯下楼
Hanover didn't come down in the elevator,
因为汉诺威这人根本就不存在
because Hanover never even existed.
道奇从一开始就扮上了
Dodge was playing the part from the beginning.
他撕下伪装
He took off his disguise,
为躲避摄像头  从逃生梯下楼
eluded the cameras by coming down a fire escape.
里斯本  他归你了
Lisbon, he's all yours.
你被捕了
You're under arrest.
有意思吧
Tell me that wasn't fun.
谈不上  不过咱俩扯平了吧
I cannot tell you that, but we are even, yes?
扯平了
Yes.
只要能让演出打响  我什么都豁得出去
I wanted the show to work. I was willing to do anything.
杀人都不在话下吗
Even kill?
我
W... I...
她吓了我一跳
She surprised me.
我当时想换掉扮演汉诺威的那身行头
When I was changing out of the Hanover costume,
那会儿那个房间里不应该有人
nobody was supposed to be in the room at that time.
一个人都不该有
Nobody.
我跟她说  我为这场演出倾尽了所有
I told her that I put every penny I had into the show
需要有汉诺威这么个人  给投资商信心
and that Hanover was necessary to give our investors a confidence
给他们吃下定心丸
and peace of mind
我告诉她  只要我赚足了钱
and that once I had the money I needed,
就会让汉诺威消失
I would make Hanover disappear
最终一切都会迎刃而解
and that everything would work out in the end.
但她不肯
But she said no.
她不想参与
She wouldn't be any part of it...
她说要告诉桑德兰
That she was going to tell Sunderland,
那一切自然就穿帮了
which of course meant that everyone would find out
全都毁了
and... that would have ruined everything.
真的  我没想到会变成这样
Yeah. I didn't mean for this to happen.
接下来发生了什么
So what happened next?
我从逃生梯逃走了  没被人看见
Uh, I left by the fire escape. No one saw me.
然后到了我停在街角的车里
And then I went and got in my car around the corner,
再把车开回来  见到了警察
and I drove up and introduced myself to the police.
这场演出要是一炮而红  我就能重回巅峰了
This was gonna be the hit show that put me back on top.
本来可以皆大欢喜的
Everyone would have benefited.
要是她没走进那扇门就好了
If only she hadn't walked through that door.
我跟她在一起的时间很少
I, um, I didn't have nearly enough time with her.
但我非常爱她  很佩服她
But I so loved the person that she was and respected her.
谢谢你们为她主持公道
Thank you for giving her justice.
这对我意义重大
It means a lot.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
不好意思  我得接个电话
Embarrassing. Uh, I have to take this.
-失陪  -接吧
- Excuse me. - Of course.
-你好  -派翠克  我是医院的希拉
- Hello? - Patrick, it's Sheila from the hospital.
医生让他醒过来了
They're bringing him out of the coma.
什么时候
When?
你得快点过来
You need to get over here.
好
Okay.
他清醒了  不过得留意着他
He's conscious, but keep an eye on him.
有事按那个钮  我们马上过来
Hit that button, and we'll be right in.
好的  谢谢  护士
Okay, thank you, nurse.
杰森·列侬  你这混蛋命够硬的
You are one tough S.O.B., Jason Lennon.
命真硬
You really are.
我在哪儿
Where am I?
出什么事了
What happened?
你在萨克拉门托  你中枪了
You're in Sacramento. You got shot.
记得吗
Do you remember that?
记得
Yes, I do.
劳拉蕾·马丁斯开的枪
Lorelei Martins.
没错  很好  很好  你头脑清楚了
Correct. Very good. Good. Your mind is clear.
现在听着  我有个问题要问你  杰森
Now listen, I have a question for you, Jason.
看着我
Look at me.
看仔细了
Look close.
认识我吗
You recognize me?
以前见过我没有
You ever seen me before?
没有
No.
确定吗  这很重要
Are you sure? It's important.
是的
Yes.
我确定
I'm sure.
这就好  谢谢
That's good to know. Thanks.
你是谁
Who are you?
一个朋友
I'm a friend.
谈点儿实际的吧  杰森
Let's face facts, Jason.
你要是恢复了  活了下来
If you recover and live,
会被控谋杀  蹲一辈子大牢
you'll spend life in prison for murder--
沦为那些变态的玩物
the plaything of monsters.
要是换做我
I just hope that if I'm ever in your shoes,
我希望能有个好朋友为我做这件事
I have a friend close enough to do this for me.
等等
Wait.
别怕
Don't be scared.
很快的
This'll be quick.
不怎么痛
Very little pain.
没事  好了
It's okay. It's all right.
没事的  我在这儿陪你
It's okay. I'm here for you.
我不会走的
I won't leave you.
来人啊  护士
Help! Nurse!
护士
Nurse!
是室颤
He's in V-fib.
把急救车推进来
Get that crash cart over here.
怎么了
What happened?
派翠克  很遗憾
Patrick, I'm sorry.
他心脏衰竭
His heart gave out.
一句话都没留下
Never said a word.